<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<faqs>
    <faq>
        <name id="general">General questions</name>
        <entry id="what_is_HaplowebMaker">
            <question>What is the purpose of the HaplowebMaker program?</question>
            <answer>HaplowebMaker is a program capable of creating Haploweb representations from FASTA alignments.</answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="what_is_Haploweb">
            <question>So and what is a Haploweb?</question>
            <answer>Haplowebs are graphical representations. Haplowebs are haplotype networks that also show which haplotypes co-occur in at least one individual of the dataset. Haplowebs have been first purposed by Jean-François Flot in his paper
            <a href="https://bmcevolbiol.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/1471-2148-10-372">Haplowebs as a graphical tool for delimiting species: a revival of Doyle's &quot;field for recombination&quot; approach and its application to the coral genus <i>Pocillopora</i> in Clipperton</a></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="how_does_it_work">
            <question>How does it work?</question>
            <answer>When the default settings are used, HaplowebMaker first calculates the evolutionary relationship of the sequences (haplotype network) via the Median-Joining-Algorithm. Afterwards the haplotype network gets visualized via a force directed graph drawing algorithm. Last, Bézier curves are added in order to connect those haplotypes that co-occur in at least one individual in the dataset.<br/><br/>However, the user has an influence on this procedure. Like this it is possible to choose another algorithm to calculate the evolutionary relationship.</answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="edit">
            <question>Is there a way to edit/improve the created Haploweb representation?</question>
            <answer>Yes, HaplowebMaker provides a specialized Image-editor that can get used to give each Haploweb a final touch. As HaplowebMaker creates standard svg-images, it is also possible to edit the created Haplotype images in programs (like Inkscape) that support this file type.</answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="cite">
            <question>How should I cite this program?</question>
            <answer>As this program was not published yet, you may cite it using the URL.</answer>
        </entry>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <name id="input">Questions concerning input</name>
        <entry>
            <question>Input files?</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="file_encoding">
            <question>File encoding</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="color_input">
            <question>How can I specify a colors?</question>
            <answer>HaplowebMaker supports colors the 140 color names, rgb(), rgba(), hsl(), hsla(), #XXX and #XXXXXX.
            integral number between</answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="find_color">
            <question>Ok, I know which color I want to have but how can I find it's #rgb representation?</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="find_color">
            <question>Alpha channel</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="find_color">
            <question>So how many colors can I specify?</question>
            <answer>16777216</answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>In art , I learned that yellow, red and blue - why </question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>YIQ</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>CMY</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>sharpness</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>web safe colors</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>same colors different screens</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
        <entry id="">
            <question>black circles</question>
            <answer></answer>
        </entry>
    <faq>
        <name id="editing"></name>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <name id="interpretation"></name>
    </faq>
</faqs>